shiftworship.com 2015-03-17

# Shift Worship | Privacy Policy

## What information do we collect?

We collect information from you when you register on the Shift Worship website or the Shift Application, place an order, subscribe to our newsletter or respond to a survey. 

When ordering or registering on Shift Worship’s website or the Shift Application, you may be asked to enter your: name, e-mail address, mailing address, phone number or credit card information. You may, however, visit our site anonymously.

## What do we use your information for?

Any of the information we collect from you may be used in one of the following ways:

  * To personalize your experience (your information helps us to better respond to your individual needs). 
  * To improve our website or application (we continually strive to improve our website or application offerings based on the information and feedback we receive from you).
  * To improve customer service (your information helps us to more effectively respond to your customer service requests and support needs).
  * To process transactions. Your information, whether public or private, will not be sold, exchanged, transferred, or given to any other company for any reason whatsoever, without your consent, other than for the express purpose of delivering the purchased product or service requested.
  * To administer a contest, promotion, survey or other site or application feature.
  * To send periodic emails. The email address you provide for order processing, may be used to send you information and updates pertaining to your order, in addition to receiving occasional company news, updates, related product or service information, etc. Note: If at any time you would like to unsubscribe from receiving future emails, we include detailed unsubscribe instructions at the bottom of each email.

## How do we protect your information?

We implement a variety of security measures to maintain the safety of your personal information when you place an order or enter, submit, or access your personal information.

We offer the use of a secure server. All supplied sensitive/credit information is transmitted via Secure Socket Layer (SSL) technology and then encrypted into our Payment gateway providers database only to be accessible by those authorized with special access rights to such systems, and are required to keep the information confidential.

After a transaction, your private information will not be stored on our servers.

## Do we use cookies?

Yes. We use cookies, session identifiers, JavaScript™, or other browser detection technology to provide users with a more pleasant online experience. A cookie is a text file that is placed on your hardware by a web page server. Cookies are uniquely assigned to you, and can only be read by a web server in the domain that issued the cookie to you. Cookies are used for convenience and to save you time when you next visit this site or application. The purpose of a cookie is to tell the web server that you have returned to a specific page, so that when you visit the site or application again, the experience will be personalized. You have the ability to accept or decline cookies. Most web browsers automatically accept cookies, but you can usually modify your browser setting to decline cookies if you prefer. If you choose to decline cookies, you may not be able to fully experience the interactive features of this site or application or other websites that you visit and you may experience technical problems receiving current information from such cookie-disabled websites.

We use cookies to help us remember and process the items in your shopping cart, understand and save your preferences for future visits and compile aggregate data about site or application traffic and site or application interaction so that we can offer better experiences and tools in the future. We may contract with third-party service providers to assist us in better understanding our site or application visitors and subscribers. These service providers are not permitted to use the information collected on our behalf except to help us conduct and improve our business.

## Third Party Advertising and Remarketing

In addition to using cookies and related technologies as described above, we also may permit certain third party companies to help us tailor advertising that we think may be of interest to users and to collect and use other data about user activities on our site or the Shift Application. These companies may deliver ads that might also place cookies and otherwise track user behavior. These companies may use information about user behavior in order to provide customized advertisements across various services and products. In the course of providing these services, products or placing advertisements, these third party companies may place or recognize a unique cookie on your computer or mobile device, and may record information to these cookies based upon your activities on our site or application and on third party websites. Each of these companies uses this information according to their own privacy and security policies. One third party company we may use for these purposes is Google. Users may opt out of Google’s use of cookies and Analytics by visiting the [Google Analytics opt-out page](https://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout). Another third party company we may use for these purposes is Flurry. Users may opt out of Flurry’s Analytics Service tracking by visiting the [Flurry Analytics Service opt-out page](http://www.flurry.com/user-opt-out.html).

## Do we disclose any information to outside parties?

We do not sell, trade, or otherwise transfer to outside parties your personally identifiable information. This does not include trusted third parties who assist us in operating our website and application, conducting our business, or servicing you, so long as those parties agree to keep this information confidential. We may also release your information when we believe release is appropriate to comply with the law, enforce our policies, or protect ours or others rights, property, or safety. However, non-personally identifiable visitor information may be provided to other parties for marketing, advertising, or other uses.

## California Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

Because we value your privacy we have taken the necessary precautions to be in compliance with the California Online Privacy Protection Act. We therefore will not distribute your personal information to outside parties without your consent.

As part of the California Online Privacy Protection Act, all users of our site and application may make any changes to their information at anytime by logging into their account page and going to the 'Edit Profile' section.

## Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act Compliance

We are in compliance with the requirements of COPPA (Childrens Online Privacy Protection Act), we do not collect any information from anyone under 13 years of age. Our website, application, products and services are all directed to people who are at least 13 years old or older.

## Online Privacy Policy Only

This online privacy policy applies only to information collected through the Shift Worship website or the Shift Application and not to information collected offline.

## Terms and Conditions

Please also visit the [Shift Worship Terms of Agreement](https://shiftworship.com/terms/) that apply to the Shift Worship website and the [Shift Application Terms and Conditions of Use](https://s3.amazonaws.com/shiftworshipstatic/shiftapp/terms.html) that apply to the Shift Application.

## Your Consent

By using the Shift Worship website or Shift Application, you consent to our online privacy policy.

## Changes to our Privacy Policy

If we decide to change our privacy policy, we will post those changes on this page, and/or update the Privacy Policy modification date below. 

This policy was last modified on February 26, 2014.

## Contacting Us

If there are any questions regarding this privacy policy you may contact us using the information below.

745 D Street

Lincoln, Nebraska 68502

United States of America

email: info [at] shiftworship.com

877-603-2346
